import { Quiz } from '../../types';

const JobsQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Jak to popisujeme?',
    name: 'Popis zaměstnání',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['nurse'],
        question: 'zdravotní sestra'
      },
      {
        answer: ['doctor'],
        question: 'doktor'
      },
      {
        answer: ['business person', 'businessman'],
        question: 'podnikatel'
      },
      {
        answer: ['secretary'],
        question: 'sekretářka'
      },
      {
        answer: ['painter'],
        question: 'malíř'
      },
      {
        answer: ['detective'],
        question: 'detektiv'
      },
      {
        answer: ['surgeon'],
        question: 'chirurg'
      },
      {
        answer: ['teacher'],
        question: 'učitel'
      },
      {
        answer: ['flight attendant'],
        question: 'stevard'
      },
      {
        answer: ['flight attendant'],
        question: 'letuška'
      },
      {
        answer: ['mail carrier'],
        question: 'poštovní doručovatel'
      },
      {
        answer: ['bell hop'],
        question: 'hotelový poslíček'
      },
      {
        answer: ['construction worker', 'laborer'],
        question: 'dělník'
      },
      {
        answer: ['handyman'],
        question: 'opravář'
      },
      {
        answer: ['waiter'],
        question: 'číšník'
      },
      {
        answer: ['cook'],
        question: 'kuchař'
      },
      {
        answer: ['accountant'],
        question: 'účetní'
      },
      {
        answer: ['fire fighter'],
        question: 'hasič'
      },
      {
        answer: ['butcher'],
        question: 'řezník'
      },
      {
        answer: ['judge'],
        question: 'soudce'
      },
      {
        answer: ['carpenter'],
        question: 'tesař'
      },
      {
        answer: ['plumber'],
        question: 'údržbář'
      },
      {
        answer: ['scientist'],
        question: 'vědec'
      },
      {
        answer: ['lawyer'],
        question: 'právník'
      },
      {
        answer: ['hairdresser'],
        question: 'kadeřník'
      },
      {
        answer: ['dentist'],
        question: 'zubař'
      },
      {
        answer: ['cashier'],
        question: 'prodavač'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default JobsQuiz;
